There's something wrong
with her.
Can you take Betsey
to the hospital?
Jess.
Jess is in A&E with Betsey.
-Oh. no.
-It's nothing serious. is it?
She's got some swelling
on the back of her head.
You can see the partially
depressed fracture just here.
What happened between you two?
You always used to be so close.
People just drift apart.
Don't know.
If the duty social worker
could come as soon as possible.
that'd be really helpful.
Who called them. Liz?
The mechanism of the fall
doesn't match the injuries.
-Could anyone have hurt Betsey?
-No.
-Jess hasn't told you?
-What are you talking about?
We're looking for
Edward Carrisford. Anyone?
Do you mind if we go
inside for a chat?
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
[monitor beeping]
-It was good to see you.
-Thanks for coming.
I was a bit surprised
that you went ahead
with the kids'
birthday party today.
Why? Why wouldn't I?
Can you tell me
what you're doing here?
In these kinds of cases.
where a very young child
is brought into hospital
with an unexplained injury.
the police and children's
services investigate jointly.
Um. she was sick.
She wasn't injured.
You haven't spoken to your wife?
Her phone must
be out of battery.
Betsey has a depressed fracture
on the back of her skull.
This kind of injury suggests
significant physical force.
Something out of the ordinary.
This is a serious matter.
Can this wait until after
I've seen my daughter?
I understand why you'd want
to go. Mr. Carrisford.
Betsey's receiving
the best possible care.
Surely you've spoken to my wife?
There must be some explanation.
We don't have any answers.
Mr. Carrisford.
that's why we're here.
I don't know
what the hell is going on.
-I just want to see my baby.
-And you will.
But first. we need to
take a look around.
We'll start in Betsey's room.
All right?
Is that necessary?
All right.
Get ready for
some expensive lawyers.
Yeah.
Jess.
[♪♪]
How did this happen?
I am completely
in the dark here.
I didn't even know
what to say to them.
Jess. why didn't you tell me?
Jess. speak to me!
You should have called me.
Jess!
Ed. please not now.
SOCO's dispatched a unit.
She took the sheets off.
That was quick.
Everything's perfect.
A bit too perfect.
How could you let me think
that this wasn't serious?
Why didn't you tell me
that she was hurt?
-Possibly domestic violence?
-Maybe.
I would have gone
to the hospital if I had known.
What are the doctors saying?
Is she going to be all right?
Is she okay?
What is going on?
Why were you hiding
in Betsey's room?
I came to get her things.
that smell like home.
[knocking on door]
Sorry to interrupt.
We're gonna have our crime
scene investigators
come in and take some
pictures in Betsey's room.
-and the kids'...
-Sorry. what crime exactly
-has been committed?
-We don't know. sir.
That's what we're here
to find out.
Sorry. sorry. sorry.
You're right. yeah.
It's been a lot.
We also need to establish
a timeline
for yesterday afternoon.
So we'll be interviewing
both of you. separately.
[door shuts]
[indistinct chatter]
Lucy will talk to the boys.
It's Christopher and Francis.
yeah?
Kit and Frankie.
What. today?
-Now?
-Please.
I don't feel comfortable
with that request.
It's much better if we do this
quickly and with your blessing.
-Mummy!
-Frank.
Frankie. big boy.
We were trying to stay out of
your way. but Frankie saw you.
Yeah. of course.
Hi. how was your party.
my love?
Mollie! Connor!
Come on. we're going.
Where's Betsey?
-She's still in the hospital.
-Where's your dad?
Oh. he went to go
and get the car.
[Jess whispering]
Don't be scared. okay?
I'm Lucy.
You're Kit. right?
Do you guys want to come
for a quick little chat?
Yeah? Let's go.
It's all right. Come on.
Frankie. did you build that?
Kit did.
Do you like blocks?
They're okay.
Here?
-I'm sorry?
-Where Betsey hurt herself.
-Was that here?
-Uh. yeah.
Or here?
No. on the right.
What does Betsey like to do?
She crawls a lot.
Were you with Betsey
and your mummy after school?
Did you have a play date?
Anyone visit?
Stop being such a baby.
Kit. come on.
You're not being helpful.
Why are you telling me off?
He's the one
not answering the question.
Oh. it's okay. I know you must
be tired after your party.
So. Kit. what time
did you get home?
After football.
Ben's mum dropped me off.
How were things
when you got home. Kit?
Dunno. nothing. Usual stuff.
And how was Betsey?
Crying.
She cries a lot in the evening.
Mum calls it the witching hour.
And so it was just you.
your brother.
your sister and your mummy.
at home last night?
Did you see Betsey fall?
Look. I appreciate this
could be a difficult situation.
It's uncomfortable for a friend
to make a social services
referral.
Yeah.
Well. we're not as close
as we used to be.
It all started in Provence.
Provence?
Shitshow.
I wish we'd never
gone away last summer.
We started to see
a different side to each other.
The sides
we normally keep hidden.
Our weaknesses.
The dark. the... the ugly.
Turns out we aren't all
as forgiving as we thought.
[indistinct chatter]
[glass clinking]
I just wanted to thank
each of you
for coming all the way
to Provence.
to spend this week
with Charlotte and myself.
It's been ten years since we met
in that dingy little room
for our first antenatal class.
Liz. Mel. Jess.
I can't think of stronger.
more inspiring mothers.
So. thank you.
Ed. Rob and Nick.
You're all far more handsome.
far more charming. and in far
better shape than myself.
And in spite of this.
we have forged a friendship
that I value so very much.
So. thank you.
Thanks for making me cry.
Andrew.
That was so sweet.
I might throw up.
Ha-ha. Hear. hear. darling.
Here's to another
ten years of friendship.
-Ten years of friendship.
-Ten years.
ALL: Cheers.
I'm going to make
a quick speech.
Oh. no!
Ting-a-ling. Ting. ting. ting.
Ting. ting. ting.
Uh. hi. sorry. guys.
I just wanted to make
a little speech as well.
I just wanted to say thank you
on behalf of the rest of us.
to the Hinmans for. no.
inviting us all out here
and introducing us all
to a level of luxury
to which I don't think
any of us have seen before.
And also for obviously
coughing up
the rental on this place.
which must have cost
a fucking shedload.
Um. but when the label.
my label. is up and running.
okay. me and Mel. we want to
invite you all backstage
with all the trimmings.
to every major venue in Europe.
And it is going to make
this quaint little villa
look like a garden shed
in comparison.
Cheers. and good luck
with it all.
-Cheers!
-Cheers.
Cheers. Cheers. Rob.
I can't believe
we're finally here.
I'm so ready for this.
Mm.
Somebody's on a mission.
Mm-hm.
-Can I have an ice lolly?
-In a second.
There's a lady
that needs a top-up.
We've got some big news
of Rob's to celebrate. right?
Yeah.
You're not excited?
I think I would be if it didn't
feel like such a massive risk.
You know.
he's put all our savings
into this new label.
and he didn't even
tell me. so...
Women preparing food.
Men drinking beer by the pool.
I didn't invite you all
on holiday
so we could revert to
traditional gender stereotypes.
Oh. well. I'm not very good
at doing nothing. so...
Oh. don't worry.
Getting shitfaced
is all I intend to do
for the next seven days.
-Oh. shit.
-Sorry.
I'm so sorry. I've got that
all over your dress.
That's the bowl you got
at the market.
Stay there.
You don't have shoes on.
Charlotte. I'm so sorry.
Maybe we could go back to the
market and buy you a new one.
No. no.
We can't. it was vintage.
What about my ice lolly?
Please?!
Please?
-I'll get it.
-Look. I'm sorry. okay?
It's just. it is
a pet peeve of mine
when kids can't say
please and thank you.
-I am on George all the time.
-Oh. we know. constantly.
We know.
Thank you.
Well. not long until we
can go on holiday.
just the grown ups.
Then we don't have to mind
our Ps and Qs. right?
Yeah. if we even want to go
on holiday together again.
Oh. come on.
-Of course we will.
As long as you
cheer the fuck up.
[laughter]
I mean. you are killing
a bit of a vibe there. Charl.
Sorry.
I am sorry. okay?
It's just these hormones I'm on.
Mood swings.
You're doing another round
of IVF.
-I'm so sorry. I didn't realise.
-I didn't know.
For my sins.
Well. good for you.
Hey.
I really do hope
it works out this time. okay?
Thank you. Jess.
How is it this time?
It's exhausting.
You know when they
say human pincushion
and roller coaster
of emotions. it's exactly that.
And for me to be in
this position again
and having to endure it
with no guarantees.
it's just. it's brutal and it's
frustrating and infuriating.
And I absolutely hate it.
Ladies. avert your gaze.
I know you're over here
ogling us young bucks.
Is that your bowl?
That's a shame.
[kids playing]
Just the last few things.
So. yester--
Sorry. I'm so sorry.
I. uh... Let me help you.
It's okay.
So walk me through
your day yesterday.
Uh. I dropped the boys off
at school.
and. uh. Betsey and I were
just at home until pick up.
Kit had football. but. um. he
was dropped back at home
at 6:30 by his friend's mom.
And after Kit came home. you
were just here with the kids.
Everything was normal?
Yeah. regular day.
It's just last night.
your story was...
..was somewhat muddled.
Well. I was exhausted and
really worried about my baby.
Okay.
And you put her to bed
as normal?
Yes. Put her to bed around 7:30.
She was irritable.
but she's teething.
Um. and the boys went down
around nine.
and I was pretty wiped out.
I went to bed too.
People think
that you can't feel alone
if you have young children.
But there's nothing lonelier
than being at home
with a screaming baby.
[camera shutter clicking]
Walk me through your movements
yesterday. Where were you?
[camera shutter clicking]
Movements?
I was at work until six.
Then I went for some drinks.
And got home?
Ten-ish.
-I want to go back.
-Can you wait?
I wanted to come with you
to the hospital.
What about the boys?
I can drop them at Mel's
or Charlotte's. maybe?
I don't want to wait.
-She needs her milk.
-All right.
You go ahead.
We'll be in touch.
Breastfeeding. it's always been
very important to her.
Yeah. My wife and I
have just had a baby.
She's evangelical about it. too.
Right. Congratulations.
-Boy or girl?
-Oh. girl. 13 weeks.
I get it.
the breastfeeding thing.
but it makes me feel
a bit redundant.
It's like that to begin with.
-Um. it's an adjustment.
-Yeah.
Makes me wonder. how long will
I be banished to the spare room?
Not sure it ever stops.
So was it the way that Betsey
was crying
that first alarmed you?
Yeah. exactly.
That's what scared me.
The noise. it was. it was wrong.
There was no indication
she was hurt?
No visual sign of injury?
Hurt? No. God. no.
I just thought she was.
I don't know. just...
-Just?
-Teething or something.
Right. and then?
And then I noticed that she'd
vomited. so I picked her up.
Did you panic?
Well. she was alone. and it was
obvious something was wrong.
-And your wife was...?
-She wasn't there.
-She was in bed.
-Sleeping?
Yes. She was exhausted.
Betsey is not a good sleeper.
Right.
And is that normal. usual. for
Jess to ignore Betsey like that?
No. not at all.
Jess is the one who always
notices these things.
She's the one that gets up in
the night to comfort the kids.
Mothers are fiercely protective
of their children.
Until they're not.
Why didn't you drive Betsey
to the hospital?
Because we have two boys.
and I was over the limit.
Thank you.
[Betsey crying]
[Betsey screaming]
[Betsey continues screaming]
-Hey.
Sorry. I didn't want to ruin
your nap.
It's fine.
I hardly slept.
You must be shattered.
Go back to sleep.
You're back at hospital
in four hours.
What if I did the wrong thing.
Nick?
What if I was too quick
to push the button?
You were put
in an impossible position.
Yeah. but I basically just
called in the cavalry
and then left her on her own
to defend herself.
You couldn't win.
no matter what you did.
[phone vibrating]
God!
Hello? Mum?
Mum! Mum. I can't understand
what you're...
Where are you?
Where are you?!
She got shitfaced and
fell over in the supermarket.
I better go and get her.
Yeah. Mum?
Mum. I'm on my way.
Yes. Stay there. Just stay
there. I'm coming to get you.
Okay.
It was all such a shock.
And naturally.
Ed's out of his mind.
Utter nonsense.
the whole situation.
I mean. Jess and Ed
are wonderful parents.
They always make me feel quite
inadequate. to be honest.
Jess has this charming way of...
Of never being irritated
when the when the children
are being particularly annoying?
That's a bit harsh.
I am disappointed with Liz.
though.
Bit dramatic to call
social services on a friend.
Everyone's very emotional
about this.
But the truth is.
nobody knows the facts.
I've seen things
that make me wonder.
Just saying. there's a fine line
between neglect and abuse.
True. but Jess is the most
attentive mother
-out of all of you.
-Excuse me!
George and I are very close.
No. of course you are.
I didn't mean that at all.
You're an amazing mum.
All right. yes.
When it comes to
Kit and Frankie.
I can somewhat see
your point.
And I'm telling you. she's never
really bonded with Betsey.
Come on. Charl.
you don't like Jess.
and you're overprotective
of Ed.
I don't know. the authorities
may know more than we do.
What? I'm just framing this
in legal terms.
Please!
We both know legal terms
fail to capture the entire
spectrum of human existence.
God. Andrew.
There were police at the party.
There were social workers.
Yeah. they must be going
through hell.
That poor baby.
Yeah. Poor Ed.
Thank you. Mel. for having them.
I've no idea how long
we'll be at the hospital.
-Of course.
-Thank you.
Oh. come on. come on. Frankie.
It's just for one night.
-No. I don't want to.
-Please. Look. You like Connor.
It's just a sleepover.
You'll have fun. I promise you.
-No! Where's Mummy?
-She's gone to go see Betsey.
Oh. I don't want to stay
at Connor's.
Please. Come here.
We don't have a choice.
Frankie. come on. You are going!
-No. I'm not going!
-Yes. you are!
-No!
-Frankie! Come on. Come here.
Frankie. look.
we don't have a choice.
-Yes. you are going. come on!
-No! No!
-Come here!
-No!
-Don't do this!
Ma'am?
Ma'am. please.
Please. Can I just see her now?
Just for a second.
I won't pick her up. I promise.
-You can come with me.
-Go home. get some rest.
A good night's sleep and
things will look a lot brighter.
I'm sure your other kids
probably need their mum. huh?
All right. honey.
come on. that's enough.
Go play. Okay?
You. too. That's enough.
Someone at the school gate said
he had a dad bod.
so he's trying to do
50 lengths a day.
I told Frankie
no more screen time.
All the others are on
their devices.
We need some chill time.
let them. no harm.
Yeah. they'll only get
square eyes.
Oh. come on. Jess.
They've been non-stop all day.
You sure you want to...?
What?
I'm just saying.
maybe slow down.
-You were...
-[laughs]
You were hitting it pretty hard
last night. so...
Looks great. Any lamb left?
-You're too late.
-No lamb.
Plenty of chicken. though.
I'm not massively
into chicken. mate.
Sorry. I didn't think
you were hungry.
Get off! You're freezing.
Why didn't you think
I was hungry?
-Because you were swimming...
-When have I ever not...
Do you want to go for a dip?
No. I don't want to go
for a dip.
Please. no.
She needs to cool down.
Rob! Come on. Rob.
she's fully dressed.
Yeah. she needs to cool off.
Don't do it. Rob.
[screams]
Don't do it. Rob! Come on.
[screaming]
Please don't. okay? I'm serious.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
[screams]
Whoa!
Jesus Christ. Rob!
Ah!
Whoa!
Stop it!
Don't encourage him!
Oh. you poor thing!
Rob! Come on.
That's not funny.
-Inappropriate.
-Honestly. Jesus.
It's a fucking holiday!
Grr.
-Cheers.
-You all right?
-Yes. I'm fine.
You always have to take it
too fucking far.
-Here. this will warm you up.
-Thank you.
-Whisky. Jess?
-I'm all right. thank you.
Jesus Christ. woman.
Do you not have any vices?
She saves all her kinks
for the bedroom.
Okay.
Stop. Enough. It's enough.
So that's what Ed says
in the bedroom?
Right. okay. you guys stay put.
Liz and I are gonna prep
some dessert.
Oh. are we?
-Yes. we are.
-I was on holiday.
I'm not talking to you.
You made that?
Mm.
Great.
Oh. poor Mel.
Rob's really not the easiest
guy in the world. is he?
No. he is not.
But that's how it's always been
with those two. isn't it?
-All fire. lust and fury.
-Mm.
Charlotte's a bit sniffy.
-Yeah. Charlotte's Charlotte.
-Hey! No!
I'm helping.
Don't take it personally.
I mean. it is what it is.
She's always going to be a bit
spiky when it comes to you.
Well. she hasn't guessed yet.
She's so clever and sharp.
Guessed what?
Oh my God.
Oh. that's so wonderful.
That's great.
It's wonderful. Is it?
-It is. isn't it?
-Yeah. yeah.
Of course. of course.
Hey.
I'm just dreading telling
the others.
Especially with Charlotte's
news.
-Yeah.
-I told Ed not to say anything
until we get back home.
Mum's the word.
[laughter]
I didn't even mean to do that.
I'm just...
He's been well trained.
-He is.
-Plates. Have you got plates?
Seriously? No. seriously.
You've got capital. right?
And you are much more creative
than you think.
And you're a mate.
That's a good partnership.
I reckon. So...
I don't know. Have a think.
-Sure.
-Listen. when it's ready.
send it to me.
If the numbers are good.
you know I'm in.
This is a chocolate raspberry
torte I baked earlier.
-Wow. That's amazing.
-Ladies and gentlemen.
that is not the only thing
that she's been baking.
-Ed!
-Come on.
-What?
-Oh. my God. Congratulations.
Oh. my God! Amazing.
How lovely.
Here's to number three.
-Number three.
-Your own little tribe.
A gaggle of Carrisfords.
Five-a-side team.
You could create your own
football strip.
Maybe you'll vaccinate this one.
-Charlotte!
-Oh. God.
-She's only kidding.
-Actually. I'm not.
It's a free world. Charlotte.
Everyone has the right to choose
what's best
for their own children.
Yeah. totally.
and also. it's not like
anyone actually dies of measles
anymore anyway.
-They do. actually.
-Well. not really.
We've had an increase
in cases lately.
Not on my watch.
Even so. we're talking about
one or two a year.
And there's been an outbreak
in whooping cough.
So all your kids should be
vaccinated against that.
If a baby under three months
gets that.
-that could be really serious.
-Would anybody like a top-up?
Statistically. it's like. low.
right?
You know why that is. Ed?
It's because the rest of us
vaccinate our children.
Yeah. but if the rest of us
have. don't we have. um...
Oh. my God.
what's that thing called?
I think you're talking about
herd immunity.
Lovely torte. Jess.
It's really...
Wait. what about
the vulnerable kids?
'Cause we've got kids at our
school who are very susceptible.
Okay. look. there's nothing
any of you can say
that would convince me to
pump chemicals into my children.
But the risk of a serious
infection. that's fine. is it?
Come on. You are living in
a bubble of privilege.
Shame on you
for not trusting the NHS.
Hey. Liz. Fuck's sake.
-A ridiculous thing to say.
-Is it? Why?
What? Well. you don't. do you?
You always go private.
-Liz.
-I'm just saying.
It's my job to protect
my children. all right?
And I take that very seriously.
Well...
Liz wasn't used to
dinner parties
where the wine flowed
that freely.
She can be good fun
when she's drunk.
but she doesn't know
when to stop.
And that night...
..things went too far.
Oh. no. No. no. no. No more.
I've got to wrangle
the little beasts.
What? It's early.
Come on. They're on holiday.
Let them play.
I'll put them to bed later
for you.
And listen.
I'm sorry about earlier.
Got a little heated.
Don't worry.
I'm happy for you.
Really happy for you guys.
You're gonna be a daddy again.
Oh. go on then.
Go and find your gorgeous wife.
[sighs]
[kids talking]
Knock. knock. Hello.
How are you getting on in here?
Oh. my goodness. I love this.
-It's time for bed. Come on.
-No.
It's been a long day. hasn't it?
We're all hot and tired.
-Come on then.
-Mum. please. one more.
All right then. just one.
and then it's straight to bed.
-Is that a deal?
-Yeah.
-Should I shut the door?
-Yes. please. Thank you.
-Bye.
Bye.
[kids talking]
-Let's make it a triple.
-Are you sure Andrew won't mind?
He wouldn't have bought it
unless he wanted us
to drink it. would he?
But that's his whisky. Rob.
Oh. well. he shouldn't have
gone to bed so early.
should he. the boring git?
Honestly. these people
got all the money in the world.
and yet they're all so
FUCKING MISERABLE!
[dogs barking]
Cheers.
Why do you even rent
a place like this?
It's fucking obscene.
Look at that.
Do you think you could maybe
give it a rest now?
Yeah.
Give what a rest?
-Pestering Ed for money.
-Pestering him?
-I mean...
-I'm not. I'm just...
I've been waiting ages for this.
and now I'm starting out
on my own. I just need...
Since you've been made
reduntant.
-Wow.
-Oh. my God. I'm sorry.
-I'm sorry. Sorry.
-Fuck me!
-I'm sorry.
-It's okay.
It's just. you know.
these are our friends.
-It's...
-Well...
They're our friends. and...
..it's a bit embarrassing.
Mm.
Oh. my God.
You're smoking!
Oh. yeah. Busted.
Got it from Rob. obviously.
-It's disgusting.
-Come here. Let me try.
Mm!
Wow.
You know. I always thought
I'd be an exceptional... stoner.
Well. you are exceptional
at everything.
Hmm. I'm a hard worker.
There's a difference.
Uh. first at Oxford.
Straight into one of London's
leading law firms.
And then made partner at 35.
Mm-hm.
Two rounds of IVF.
a miscarriage.
a body that refuses
to follow its natural.
nurturing instincts
and instead provides
a radically hostile environment
for vulnerable life forms.
Oh. God. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Of course. I'm an idiot.
I knew you'd been trying
for a while.
You know what? It's fine.
Really. it's okay.
I just said I would try
one last time.
For Andrew.
Oh. God.
He wouldn't make you do
anything you wouldn't want to.
Mm.
God. no. Of course not.
Andrew's a good man.
Yeah.
He is a good man.
He deserves better.
Whoa. Charl?
No. I mean...
I feel guilty that I don't...
..I don't love him
the way he wants to be loved.
Charl. I am sure
that is not true.
What about you?
-Huh?
-You're on number three.
Yeah.
Are you excited?
Uh. yeah.
Totally. I mean. we both are.
Of course.
There's just this. this.
this tiny part of me...
..that hopes it won't ruin
what we already have.
Does that make sense?
[dogs barking]
Oh!
Oh. boys!
Frankie?
Sam? Sammie?
Shit!
Sam! Frankie!
Frankie! Sam!
Okay. I'm gonna check the villa.
You said you put them to bed.
All right.
I'm gonna call the owners now
and see if they can let us...
Sam! Frankie! Come on.
-Frankie. Come on.
-Sam.
Two of our children.
they've gone missing.
We think they must be lost.
Tell them
they're not strong swimmers.
-I know.
-Check the pool.
Sam!
It's pitch black out here.
They're only seven-years-old.
So they're going to be
frightened as anything.
We need to have the numbers
of all the neighbours
in the area.
Uh. Frankie and Sam.
they wandered off.
What do you mean.
they wandered off?
-Ed said you put them to bed.
-I fell asleep
and they were in the den.
and now they're...
-Fell asleep?!
What are you talking about. Liz?
Frankie can't swim.
What if he fell into a pool?
They're going to be fine.
You need to keep calm.
They're not gonna be fine!
Where's Ed?
He went that way.
They're checking the...
Jess. we're going to find them.
It's okay. Frankie! Sam!
Ed!
Look. here. there might be
somebody calling.
-I fell asleep.
-It's okay.
Don't worry. Hello?
Frankie!
-Jess.
-Frankie.
Where's Ed?
He went left
at the top of the gate.
Sam!
Come on. guys. it's all right.
We won't be cross.
Just come out.
Sam!
Frankie?
Sammie!
Frankie!
They're here!
Got them.
-Frankie!
-Dad!
Here he is.
-Sam.
-There he is. He's fine.
-He's fine.
-There you go.
Oh. Sam.
-You okay?
-He's okay.
-Come here. you silly sausage.
You okay?
You scared me.
Don't do that again. okay?
Okay.
You all right?
It's okay.
Everyone was on the verge
of exploding that night.
It was like there was
something in the air.
Tensions were sky high.
God help you
if you're ever the one
to put Jess' kids in danger.
My mouth feels like
I've got a dead dog in it.
-I didn't sleep at all.
-Yeah. it's called a hangover.
Mm.
You okay?
[Jess sighs]
You know last night
with the kids?
You were drinking.
We were all drinking.
But you were drunk.
And. you know. Frankie and Sam.
they could have gotten
seriously hurt.
they could have fallen
into that pool.
They didn't.
But you were meant to
look after them.
Okay.
Is this... Are you..?
I can't believe
you'd think I'm...
Let's drop it.
What if I don't want to drop it?
I'm just saying. Liz.
-Maybe. maybe take a minute.
-From what?
Jess. I fell asleep.
The boys are fine.
I don't know why you're
making such a big thing of this.
I know. It was more important
to get wasted
than look after my children.
I get it.
You know what. Jess?
This is...
This is actually the first
holiday that I've had in years.
You know. I do 60-hour weeks.
I am constantly tired.
I've never had enough sleep or
spent enough time with my kids.
or. God forbid. done something
for myself. like go to the gym.
And my house.
it's always a mess.
But there's nothing I can do
about that. Nothing.
Because my family are relying on
my income to pay the mortgage.
I know.
We all need to relax. Liz.
I'm just saying. maybe it's time
to take a break
from the alcohol.
This is my break. Jess. Now.
This is it. It's happening.
Next week I'm going to be
back at work.
and I won't even have time
to breathe.
So. please. please.
for the love of God.
will you just let me.
let me be sloppy.
Let me be lazy and drunk.
Yeah.
Just for one short week. please.
Without all the comments.
You're acting just like
your mom.
Fuck off!
Okay. Look. Liz.
you can do what you want.
but just don't do it over
my children. okay?
Okay. yeah.
Yeah. No. I shouldn't be
juggling a career
and parenting around the...
Oh. dear. What a terrible
example I am for your kids.
Sorry. Jess. Sorry I've been
busy saving lives
while you've been filling bento
boxes with homemade vegan sushi.
That's not what I'm saying.
-Yes. it is. It is!
-No!
No. you. you have
the kind of perfect.
privileged life that 99% of
women will never. ever have.
Okay. Yeah. my life's
not perfect. Uh-uh.
No. but you are. aren't you?
And you make it very clear
that the rest of us.
we'll never compare.
Come on. guys. hurry up!
I knew Jess
would never trust me again.
We hardly saw each other
after that holiday.
I rarely do school pickup.
but when I did. we'd be. like.
opposite ends of the playground.
And then after she had Betsey.
it was like...
It was like we'd never
been friends.
And then that night.
she came into A&E.
and I had to ask myself.
was she capable
of hurting her own child.
or was she protecting
someone else?
Because she clearly knew more
than she was telling me.
[pump whirring]
[breathing heavily]
-Liz?
-Yes.
Look. I've been reflecting
and I think...
I think I was a bit. um.
a bit hasty
starting all the child
protection procedures.
I'm afraid that horse has
bolted. as well you know.
No. I just assumed that once
you'd spoken to the parents
and you know.
established what had happened.
then there'd be no reason
for further intervention.
But we haven't established
what happened.
The mother was vague
and the father was clueless.
Look. Jess just doesn't trust
me enough to tell me. so...
No. honestly. this is absolutely
not necessary.
Because those children
are safe and they're loved.
Dr. Burgess. we know that
you have a personal relationship
with the family. but you made
this call based on what you saw.
Yeah. but everything's
moving so fast.
Please. believe me when I say
this has to have been
an accident.
-It just has to.
-Thank you. Elizabeth.
Right now. for obvious reasons.
I'm going to have to ask you
to leave.
I'm convinced this isn't
an accidental injury.
Mm. We weren't able to interview
either of the boys on their own
without Dad in the room.
And the interview with the
youngest son was troubling.
He was extremely distressed.
I'd say there's some
undiagnosed behavioural issues.
You okay? What's going on?
Why won't they let me
see Betsey?
Take a seat. Mr. Carrisford.
I haven't seen Betsey
since yesterday.
You both need
to sign this first.
before you can see her.
You'll be agreeing that while
the investigation takes place.
you will not be alone
with any of your children.
Any of our children?
That's not going to happen.
This is for the safety
of your children.
You've been to our home.
You've talked to my family.
We don't need social services.
-We're a decent family.
-Unfortunately. Mr. Carrisford.
child neglect and abuse don't
discriminate based on wealth.
This is a witch hunt.
Can I see your manager
or director?
You can if you like. but I doubt
she'll be able to help you.
The law states that when
a child is at risk of harm.
children's services. that's me.
must take steps to protect them.
How long does this go on for?
Until we know exactly
what happened last night.
Can we just slow down a minute?
I'm sure there's a perfectly
innocent explanation
for how Betsey got hurt. right?
She fell.
I told you that she fell.
Please sign. Things will go
more smoothly if you comply.
I'm not signing away
our children.
No.
Then we'll have to place
your children into foster care.
You can't do that.
YOU CAN'T TAKE OUR CHILDREN!
[Betsey crying]
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org